PAFF：Wake up~Can you hear me?
PAFF：일어나. 내 목소리 들리니?
PAFF：It's already been three months since everything happened.
PAFF：그때 이후로 벌서 3 개월이나 지났네.그 동안 잘 지낸 거지?
Leo：From the bottom of our hearts, we promise that from here on out,
PAFF：Vanessa가 세계를 위험 속으로 몰아넣었던 이후로
PAFF：After averting the crisis that Vanessa threatened the world with...
Leo：저희는 향후 고대문명을 비밀리에 사용하는 것이 아닌,
PAFF：A.R.C. abolished the Library's facilities
PAFF：A.R.C.는 Library의 사용을 폐지했고
Leo：and will be transparent with all the content of our research
Leo：연구 내용에 있어서도 모든 것을 공개하며
PAFF：and used other types of server technology to replace the operations of the virtual internet
PAFF：지금은 다른 서버 기술로 정신 네트워크 운영을 대신하고 있어.
Leo：by making it available to the public
Leo：투명성이 높은 경영 방침을 지향하도록 하겠습니다.
Leo：Starting from today, we will implement serious changes to our internal structure
Leo：또한, 사내 개혁 실시를 통하여
Leo：For the development of society and humanity
Leo：사회와 인류 발전에 있어서도
PAFF：Of course, many people are unable to accept such a decision
PAFF：물론 많은 사람들이 현실을 받아들이지 못하고 있지만
Leo：we will seriously reconsider our position in society and the direction we are headed...
Leo：저희의 사회적 입지와 방향성에 대해 다시 한번 재검토하는 계기를 마련할 수 있도록...
PAFF：Especially those who lost their loved ones as a result of what happened
PAFF：특히 이번 사건으로 사랑하는 사람을 잃은 사람들...
PAFF：But after a period of time most people returned to their normal lives
PAFF：그래도 대부분의 사람들이 어느
PAFF：Time gradually diluted all that had occurred...
PAFF：이렇게 시간이 흘러가면서 모든 것이 잊혀져가겠지...
PAFF：After graduating from university, NEKO became a professional streamer musician
PAFF：NEKO 씨는 아카데미를 졸업한 후, 편곡 전문 스트리머가 됐어.
PAFF：Besides her normal content of music, games and random gossip
PAFF：음악말고도 게임이나 가십 거리 등등 폭넓게 활동하고 있는 것 같아.
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Yo-ho! NEKO's here!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：야호~! NEKO 등장!
PAFF：she also started a new series
PAFF：그리고 채널을 새롭게 하나 개설했는데
PAFF：where she actively goes out to help the victims that were affected by the incident with Vanessa
PAFF：Vanessa 사건의 피해자들을 돕는 활동을 하고 있어.
Victim：We don't need help from you internet addicts. Please, go away...
피해자：당신들 같은 네트워크 중독자의 도움 따위는 필요 없어요. 돌아가주세요...
PAFF：It's not easy, but she doesn't get discouraged
PAFF：조금 고생을 하는 것 같지만, 그렇다고 낙심한다거나 그러는 건 아니야.
PAFF：She used money she made from her music and streams to set up a foundation
PAFF：음악과 방송으로 번 돈으로 자선 단체를 설립하고
PAFF：that donates to the people affected and related illnesses
PAFF：피해자들과 후유증을 앓고 있는 사람들을 위해 모금 활동을 벌이고 있어.
PAFF：At night, she's still a die-hard music fan
PAFF：이런 NEKO 씨이지만, 밤에는 여전히 음악을 좋아하는 NEKO 씨이기도 해.
PAFF：As for Xenon, he got back to performing with a band after everything was over
PAFF：Xenon 씨는 그때 이후로 밴드 활동을 다시 시작했어.
NEKO#ΦωΦ：Not bad~!
NEKO#ΦωΦ：고생했어~!
PAFF：Xenon's sister Shannon,
PAFF：Xenon 씨의 여동생 Shannon은
PAFF：she gradually shed the effect that the virtual internet had on her
PAFF：그때 이후로 조금씩 정신 네트워크의 영향으로부터 벗어나고 있고
PAFF：and her condition started to improve
PAFF：병세도 많이 호전됐어.
PAFF：A.R.C. kept begging Xenon to return
PAFF：A.R.C.는 Xenon에게 계속 복귀하기를 요청하고 있는 것 같아.
PAFF：But no matter how generous their offers were, no matter what position they promised
PAFF：하지만 아무리 좋은 대우나 직위를 제안한다고 해도
PAFF：Xenon refused to accept
PAFF：Xenon 씨는 전혀 받아들일 생각이 없는 것 같아.
PAFF：Perhaps in his heart,
PAFF：마음속엔 아직도 뿌리치지 못하는 한 앞으로 나아갈 수 없는 과거가 있기 때문이겠지.
PAFF：After the dissolution of Baro,
PAFF：Baro 패거리가 와해돼버린 후,
PAFF：the position of JOE's bar in the inner circles grew higher and higher
PAFF：JOE 씨의 술집도 사회적 입지가 조금씩 올라가면서
PAFF：JOE became more and more like Uncle Saxon
PAFF：JOE 씨도 조금씩 Saxon 숙부의 모습을 닮아가고 있는 것 같아.
PAFF：and some familiar faces could be seen hanging around, just like before
PAFF：가게에선 익숙한 얼굴을 자주 볼 수 있는데
PAFF：Mr. Neumann decided to move to Node 13,
PAFF：Neumann 씨는 Node 13으로 이민을 결심하고
PAFF：continuing to research the unsolved mysteries of his ancestors with Sasha
PAFF：Sasha 씨와 함께 계속해서 아직 풀리지
PAFF：Humanity's interest in ancient technology didn't disappear
PAFF：인간의 고대 문명에 대한 호기심은 여전히 사라지지 않은 모양이야.
PAFF：and missions of A.R.C.'s Exploration Team continued
PAFF：A.R.C.의 탐사대는 여전히 임무를 수행하고 있어.
PAFF：Occasionally, they run into someone with motives different from their own
PAFF：도중에 가끔씩 목적이 다른 사람들과 마주치기도 하는 것 같지만
ConneR：Oh? You again?
ConneR：뭐야? 당신이었나?
ConneR：Keep up the hard work
ConneR：수고가 많군.
PAFF：Rin was able to break free of A.R.C.'s control,
PAFF：Rin은 A.R.C.의 지배로부터 벗어나
PAFF：concealing her Architect identity and living with Sagar
PAFF：아키텍트의 신분을 숨긴 채 Sagar 씨와 함께 지내고 있어.
PAFF：She also returned to Node 03 to look for her past memories
PAFF：그녀도 Node 03으로 돌아가 과거 기억들의 단서를 찾고 있는 것 같아.
Rin：Ah! Oh...
Rin：아앗!....
Rin：I'm s-so sorry!
Rin：죄, 죄송합니다!
Rin：Wah!
Rin：꺅...!
Daigo：Chief, here's the part you asked for
Daigo：팀장, 찾으시던 부품 여깄습니다.
PAFF：Last time we heard from Nora
PAFF：마지막으로 받았던 Nora 씨의 소식으로는
Nora：Thank you, just put it there
Nora：고마워, 거기에 놔 둬.
PAFF：she was just about finished repairing ROBO_Head
PAFF：곧 ROBO_Head의 수리가 끝난다고 했던 것 같아.
Nora："NORA"
Nora：「NORA」
PAFF：Then... there's me
PAFF：그리고... 나는...
PAFF：Once again, I returned to the stage as PAFF as well as doing performances on the street
PAFF：나는 다시 PAFF 로 돌아와 스테이지에서 길거리에서 노래를 하고 있어.
PAFF：I accepted the fact that I was both Aroma and Kaori...
PAFF：내 자신이 Aroma이자 Kaori라는 사실을 받아들였어...
PAFF：We... are PAFF
PAFF：PAFF가, 바로 우리들이라는 것을.
PAFF：Though I don't know what the future holds for humanity now that Vanessa is gone
PAFF：Vanessa가 사라진 후, 인간의 미래가 어떻게 변할지는 알 수 없지만
PAFF：we're going to continue to use music to give power and courage to everyone
PAFF：우리가 음악으로 모두에게 주는 힘과 용기는
PAFF：It may not be much
PAFF：아마 조금일 지라도
PAFF：but we'll try to use everything in our power to change this world,
PAFF：그래도, 이 세상을 바꾸기 위해서 최선을 다할 생각이야.
PAFF：because that's all we can do
PAFF：이것이 바로 우리가 할 수 있는 유일한 거니까.
PAFF：This... is our story.
PAFF：이것이... 우리들의 이야기.